hilalplaza.com 2013-10-05

# Islamic Online Education and Online Degree Programs - Graduate, Masters. Doctorate, PhD

HilalPlaza.com takes your privacy seriously. The following provides details on our privacy policy.  

**NOTICE:** Visit [ http://onguardonline.gov/](http://onguardonline.gov/) for practical tips from the federal government and the technology industry to help you guard against Internet fraud, secure your computer and protect your personal information.

** Scope of This Privacy Policy **

·         This policy covers HilalPlaza.com and IqraSense.com

·         This policy covers how HilalPlaza.com treats personal information that HilalPlaza.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of HilalPlaza.com products and services. Personal information includes your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

·         This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that HilalPlaza.com does not own or have control on, or to people that HilalPlaza.com does not employ or manage. 

** Information Collection and Use**

_ General_

·         HilalPlaza.com collects personal information when you buy products from HilalPlaza.com. HilalPlaza.com also collects your name and Email address when distributing some information. This information that HilalPlaza.com distributes is owned by HilalPlaza.com, or publicly available or copyright-free or permitted by copyright owners. 

·         When you buy products from HilalPlaza.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 

·         HilalPlaza.com collects information about your transactions with us. 

·         HilalPlaza.com automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address and the page you request. 

·         HilalPlaza.com and IqraSense.com uses information for the following general purposes: fulfill your requests for products and services, to send you periodic updates on our products and services, improve our services, contact you, and conduct research. 

·         When receiving information from HilalPlaza.com, you can always unsubscribe from our mailing list. 

_ Age Limitation _

·         HilalPlaza.com does not collect any information related to age as most of its products and services are considered safe for all ages. 

** Information Sharing and Disclosure**

·         HilalPlaza.com and IqraSense.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

o        We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

o        We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of HilalPlaza.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

o        We transfer information about you if HilalPlaza.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, HilalPlaza.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

·         HilalPlaza.com displays targeted advertisements based on the page information and content as operated by certain advertising networks. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 

o        HilalPlaza.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

o        HilalPlaza.com advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

** Cookies**

·         HilalPlaza.com may set and access HilalPlaza.com [ cookies](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/cookies/) on your computer. 

·         HilalPlaza.com lets other sites that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to HilalPlaza.com's cookies. 

** Confidentiality and Security **

·         We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

·         We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. 

** Changes to this Privacy Policy**

·         HilalPlaza.com may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your HilalPlaza.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

** Questions and Suggestions **

·         If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at: 

HilalPlaza.com  
Customer Care - Privacy Policy Issues  
22951 Los Alisos Blvd

Mission Viejo, CA 92691

_ Effective Date: November 1, 2005_
